What happened (to) mommy's make-up?
妈妈的化妆品怎么了
What do you have all over your face?
你脸上都是什么
Umm, chopstick.
额  粉笔
Oh, that's not chopstick.
哦  这可不是粉笔
Not chopstick?
不是粉笔吗
Umm-hmm, that's momy's lipstick.
嗯哼  这是妈妈的口红
Oh, lipstick? I want lipstick.
啊  口红  我喜欢口红
Where did you get it?
你从哪儿拿的
From mommy's make-up.
妈妈的化妆品里面
And did mommy tell you not to play the make-up?
我有没有告诉过你不要玩妈妈的化妆品
Umm-hmm.
嗯哼
So why did you go playing the make-up again?
那怎么又玩
I won't go again.
我以后不会了
I don't touch mommy's make-up.
我没有碰妈妈的化妆品
Oh, but I think you did touch my make-up
但我觉得你有哦
cuz it's all of your mouth.
看你满嘴都是
-Mommy. -Hem? -Could you take it down, mom?
-妈咪  -嗯  -能帮我擦掉吗  妈妈
Oh, you don't like the color?
怎么  你不喜欢这个颜色
Nope.
嗯
Where's Ben?
本在哪儿
Ben's in the room.
他在房间里
Go get him and tell him to come here. Hurry.
去把他叫来  快点儿